

Tomas Silny Fullstack Developer

M. R. Stefanika 41, Cifer, Slovakia +421 904 102 216 · tomas.silny7@gmail.com

GitHub, My portfolio

Date / Place of birth 04/20/1999, Trnava, Slovakia, Europe

Nationality

Slovak

Skills
React, React Native, NextJS
JavaScript
HTML & CSS
C#/.NET
Java
PHP, Laravel
Git
SQL
Python
С
Computer Networking
Android Development
Languages
Slovak
English (B2)

Profile

My name is Tomas Silny and I am a Software Developer. I have more than 4 years of experience in software development. I am proficient in Web and Mobile development using React, Laravel (PHP), C#/.NET, and SQL databases. I like to design apps, websites, or anything that people can see. I have experience doing commercial apps and websites as a fullstack developer for my customers, or just for fun during my study at university. Except for programming in my free time, I play the piano, ride the bicycle or watch movies or TV shows. I am reliable, I take care of details and I am optimistic. I like to learn new things, especially in IT and software development.

Employment History

Fullstack Developer, Softlogic Software

January 2022 — Present (softlogicsoftware.com, self-employed, my website)

- Development of Web and Mobile apps for customers and companies
- Solved complex problems using the latest technologies such as React, Laravel, and cloud services
- Coded software updates and maintained already developed systems

Fullstack Developer, SensoHealth Solutions s.r.o.

June 2021 — January 2022 (sensohealth.org)

- I'm currently working on this project under Softlogic Software as selfemployed and I was working for this company from December 2019 to June 2021 as part-time developer during my study
- The company is focused on research in human body motion using special 3D cameras. We are analysing Gait and Posture of different patients
- Designed and developed Web and Mobile apps for neurologists using React, Laravel, C#/.NET and Azure services.
- Coded software updates, designed new functions, wrote documentation
- Managed a small team of developers

Education

MSc. in Project Management, EDU Effective Business School, Prague, Czech Republic (professional degree - online study)

November 2021 – September 2022

Bachelor of Computer Science, Matej Bel University, Banska Bystrica, Slovakia

September 2018 — June 2021

Courses

Programming in C language, IT Learning Slovakia

February 2018 — March 2018

CISCO CCNA 1 & 2, CISCO NETACAD

November 2016 - December 2017

Extra-curricular activities

1st place at Young Computer Scientist competition, University of Economics, Bratislava, Slovakia

April 2018

 Developed an app for scanning dangerous products on the market. Source code available on my GitHub (tomassilny)

Junior Internet competition Slovakia, Slovak Technical University, Bratislava, Slovakia

February 2017

 Price of Dean of the Slovak Technical University, Bratislava for app helping our environment. Available on my GitHub (tomassilny)

Portfolio

ByteShare.net, Web Development

September 2021 — Present

- File manager that allows to upload large files including remote upload from any URL, via FTP and my own built API
- Built using Laravel, Python, Bootstrap and JavaScript

CodeDocs.org, Web Development

March 2021 — April 2021

- Website generated using Wikipedia API. This includes more than 5000 generated pages about software development and IT.
- Built using HTML & CSS, PHP, JavaScript and MySQL.

Please visit my online interactive portfolio at: softlogicsoftware.com/tomassilny